Guide to the Lee P. Brown Papers, 1954-2013 MS 509
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XVIII: Addendum A, 1979-2013
  - Sub-Series K: Post-Mayor Career
    - "Community Policing: The American Experience", ca. 2010 (Box 113, Folder 32)
    - Eastern Downtown Houston Development International Zone Project, 2009-11-01 (Box 113, Folder 33)
    - Eastern Kentucky University, College of Justice and Safety, 2009-03-18 (Box 113, Folder 34)
    - "Focus on Public Safety", 2008-10 (Box 113, Folder 35)
    - "Historically Black Colleges and Universities Safety Initiative", ca. 2005 (Box 113, Folder 36)
    - Jinshan Development Forum, 2004-10-28 (Box 113, Folder 37)
    - National Association for Justice Information Systems, 2005-09-21 (Box 113, Folder 38)
    - "Policing in the 21st Century: Community Policing", ca. 2010 (Box 113, Folder 39)
    - Shezhen Police Academy, 2013-11-20 (Box 113, Folder 40)
    - "Two Takes: Drugs Are a Major Social Problem, We Cannot Legalize Them", 2008-07-25 (Box 113, Folder 41)